Finding Aid for Clare E. Hoffman Papers 1934-1962
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Legislative files 1943-1962, 24.5 linear feet
  - 1961-1962
    - Public Works (Box 48)
    - Radio-Clear Channel (Box 48)
    - Reorganization Plans (Box 48)
    - Reorganization Plans, 3 folders (Box 49)
    - Rules Committee (Box 49)
    - Rural Electric Administration (Box 49)
    - School Construction (Box 49)
    - Sleeping Bear (Box 49)
    - Small Business (Box 49)
    - States Rights (Box 49)
    - Supreme Court (Box 49)
    - Taxes
      - General (Box 49)
      - Banks (Box 49)
      - Dividends (selection taken) (Box 49)
      - Dupont Stock (Box 49)
      - Excise (Box 49)
        - General (Box 49)
        - Telephone (Box 49)
      - Gasoline (Box 49)
      - Highways (Box 49)
      - Income (Box 49)
      - Income (Box 50)
      - Interstate Commerce (Box 50)
      - Legislation (H.R. 10650) (Box 50)
      - Mutual Insurance (Box 50)
      - Truckers (Box 50)
    - Television (Box 50)
    - Un-American Activities Committee (Box 50)
    - Unemployment Compensation (Box 50)
    - Unions (Box 50)
    - United Nations (Box 50)
    - Voting (Box 50)
    - Wage-Hour (Box 50)
    - War (Box 50)
    - Wilderness
- Bills file 1938-1962, 5 linear feet
  A biennial series, except for 1938-1942, the Bills File is arranged sequentially, beginning first with House Resolutions, and after that with the House Bills. These files concern primarily resolution and legislation introduced by Hoffman. Files consisting of only the printed copy of the bill have been eliminated. These are Hoffman's working files and contain background correspondence, memoranda, and drafts showing changes in the proposed legislation.
  - List of CEH bills and resolutions 1935-1944 (Box 50)
  - 1938
    - CEH bills (also bills not introduced) (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 496. Bill to investigate NLRB and Operation of Wagner Act (Box 50)
  - 1939
    - H. Res. 197. Request of information from Attorney General (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 287. Committee to investigate collections by UMW, J.L. Lewis, etc. (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 313 and 314. Bohn Aluminum Strike (Box 50)
    - H.R. 4906. Bill to prevent transportation of strikers (Box 50)
    - H.R. 7440. Bill to prevent interference with transportation of goods in interstate or foreign commerce (Box 50)
    - H.R. 7582. Define, prevent and punish interference with interstate commerce (Box 50)
    - H.R. 7606. Bill to limit expenditure of federal funds (Box 50)
    - Tin Act amendment 1937-1939 (Box 50)
  - 1940
    - Miscellaneous bills, amendments, resolutions (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 402 and 425. American Youth Congress (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 472 and 486. Requesting information from Secretary of Agriculture (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 505. Requesting information relating to printing of findings in Bridges case (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 559. Burr Oak incident (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 612 (and others). Discrimination against union or non-union workers in national defense program (Box 50)
    - H. R. 987. Exemption of House of David from Social Security Act (Box 50)
    - H.R. 9978. Noninterference with National Defense Silver Purchase Act repeal (1936-1940) (Box 50)
  - 1941
    - H.R. 38. Committee to investigate nonunion discrimination on defense work (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 144. Committee to investigate union activities in the District of Columbia (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 265. Referendum on sending AEF and Naval Forces attacking ships (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 330. Requesting information from Secretary of Navy regarding discrimination because of union or non-union affiliation (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 346. John L. Lewis and UMWA (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 349. To call Westbrook Pegler before Labor Committee (Box 50)
    - H.R. 1403. "Right to Work" Defense Act (Box 50)
    - H.R. 1406. Prevent district of federal employees holding two or more jobs (Box 50)
    - H.R. 1407. "Noninterference with National Defense" Act (Box 50)
    - H.R. 1908. National Defense Act (Box 50)
    - H.R. 1814. Right to Work Act (Box 50)
    - H.R. 2267. To prevent district or federal employees from driving taxis (Box 50)
    - H.R. 4040. To prevent interference with Lend-Lease Act (Box 50)
    - H.R. 4966. To amend NLRA (Box 50)
    - H.R. 5015. To register labor organizations (1937-1941) (Box 50)
    - H.R. 5696. Restoration of right to work (Box 50)
    - H.R. 5923. To amend NLRA by striking closed shop provision (Box 50)
    - H.R. 5924. To amend Selective Training and Service Act of 1940 (Box 50)
    - H.R. 6068. Unions Registration and Elections Act of 1941 (Box 50)
  - 1942
    - H.Res. 328. Filing of statement by government employee using assumed name (Box 50)
    - H.Res. 425. To investigate Federal Union, Inc. and similar organizations (Box 50)
    - H.Res. 464. Committee to question L. Metcalfe Walling (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 534. To investigate Secretary of Navy Knox (Box 50)
    - H. Res. 574. Requesting Secretary of Labor to advise as to employees formerly in labor organizations (Box 50)
    - H.R. 6471. To amend Civil Service Act to eliminate Congressmen from benefits (Box 50)
    - H.R. 6808. To equalize compensation of men in armed forces serving in combat areas (Box 50)
    - H.R. 7413. To relieve businessmen from OPA forms A and B (Box 50)
  - 1943-1944 (Box 51)
    - H. Res. 78. To end practices interfering with success of armed forces (Box 51)
    - H. Res. 90. Requesting information about Walter Winchell (Box 51)
    - H. Res. 108. Requesting information about Walter Winchell (Box 51)
    - H. Res. 260. Committee to investigate statement about bribe in CIO publication (Box 51)
    - H. Res. 430. Requesting information as to Walter Winchell's military status (Box 51)
    - H. Res. 478. Declaring policy of National War Labor Board (Box 51)
    - H. Res. 484. Requesting information from AG re: Jergens' employees (Box 51)
    - H. Res. 502. Asking AG whether Rudolf Hess had been requested to testify as witness (Box 51)
    - H. Res. 503. Proclamation of Day of Prayer (Box 51)
    - H. Res. 568. Asking AG the number of refugees coming into U.S. by plane (Box 51)
    - H.R. 1472 (and 5006). To protect union employees (re: dues, etc.) (Box 51)
    - H.R. 1473. To preserve employment and seniority rights of union members in service (Box 51)
    - H.R. 1486. Induct strikers and others interfering with war effort (Box 51)
    - H.R. 2033. Prohibit political contributions by labor unions (Box 51)
    - H.R. 2463. Prohibit political contributions by labor unions and chambers of commerce (Box 51)
    - H.R. 2499. To aid in preservation of freedom of speech and press (Box 51)
    - H.R. 3893. Furloughs for overseas servicement (Box 51)
    - H.R. 4490. To amend Navy Code (Box 51)
  - 1945-1946 (folders not listed) (Box 51)
  - 1947-1948 (folders not listed) (Box 52)
  - 1949-1950 (folders not listed) (Box 52)
  - 1951-1952 (folders not listed) (Box 52)
  - 1953-1954 (folders not listed) (Box 53)
  - 1955-1956 (folders not listed) (Box 53)
  - 1957-1958 (folders not listed) (Box 54)
  - 1959-1960 (folders not listed) (Box 54)
  - 1961-1962 (folders not listed) (Box 54)
- Political files 1934-1962, 14.5 linear feet
  Consisting of yearly files for 1934 and 1936-1946, and then biennially thereafter, the Political Files includes the earliest extant Hoffman papers. The files for the 1930s consist primarily of copies of Hoffman's newspaper advertisements and campaign brochures, and political speeches. In 1940 the character of the files changes to include correspondence, political mailings, speeches, and general campaign materials. To be noted here are files maintained by Hoffman of his interaction with the six Republican county committees that fell within his district. These files also document Hoffman's relationship with the Republican State Central Committee, the national Republican party, and various other Republican organizations.
  - 1934
    - Advertisements, miscellaneous (Box 55)
  - 1936
    - Advertisements
      - Primary (Box 55)
      - General Election (Box 55)
  - 1937
    - Hoffman Speeches (Box 55)
  - 1938
    - Advertisements (Box 55)
      - Primary (Box 55)
      - General Election (Box 55)
  - 1939
    - Hoffman Speeches (Box 55)
  - 1940
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Adverse (Box 55)
    - Advertisements
      - Primary (Box 55)
      - General Election (Box 55)
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 55)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Barry County Republican Committee (Box 55)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee (Box 55)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 55)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Endorsements (Box 55)
    - Expense statements (Box 55)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Form letters (Box 55)
    - Foulkes, George (Box 55)
    - Fourth District Congressional Committee (Box 55)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Hoffman speeches (Box 55)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Letters from the People column (Box 55)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 55)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Petitions (Box 55)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Racette, Felix A. (Box 55)
    - Releases (Box 55)
    - Republican National Committee (also includes Republican National Congressional Committee) (Box 55)
    - Republican State Central Committee (Box 55)
    - Republican organizations (Box 55)
    - Requests for contributions (Box 55)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - St. Joseph County Republican Committee (Box 55)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Van Buren County Republican Committee (Box 55)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Workers (Box 55)
    - XYZ (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
  - 1941
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 55)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee (Box 55)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 55)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Endorsements (Box 55)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 55)
    - Hoffman speeches (Box 55)
    - Invitations (Box 56)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Publicity (Box 56)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Republican Congressional Committee (Box 56)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 56)
    - Republican Small Business Committee (Box 56)
    - Republican State Central Committee (Box 56)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - St. Joseph County Republican Committee (Box 56)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Van Buren County Republican Committee (Box 56)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
  - 1942
    - Advertisements
      - Primary (Box 56)
      - General Election (Box 56)
  - 1943
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 56)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Barry County Republican committee (Box 56)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee (Box 56)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 56)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Dancey, S.N. (Box 56)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Endorsements (Box 56)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Hoffman speeches, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Poems (Box 56)
    - Publicity (Box 56)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 56)
    - Republican State Central Committee (Box 56)
    - Republican miscellaneous (Box 56)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Van Buren County Republican Committee (Box 56)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - XYZ (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
  - 1944
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Advertisements
      - Primary (Box 56)
      - General Election (Box 56)
      - For Bernard T. Foley (Box 56)
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 56)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Barry County Republican Committee (Box 56)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee (Box 56)
    - Bricker, John W. (Box 56)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 56)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 56)
    - Campaign materials, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Campaign support (Box 56)
    - Commendatory (Box 57)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (political activities), 2 folders (Box 57)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Dewey, Thomas E (Box 57)
    - Editorials (district) (Box 57)
    - Endorsements (Box 57)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Foley, Bernard T. (Box 57)
    - Form letters (Box 57)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Hill, R.L. (Box 57)
    - Hoffman speeches (Box 57)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - King, John R (Box 57)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Letters from the People column (Box 57)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 57)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Petitions (Box 57)
    - Poems (Box 57)
    - Propaganda (Box 57)
    - Publicity (Box 57)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Receipts (Box 57)
    - Releases (Box 57)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 57)
    - Republican National Congressional Committee (Box 57)
    - Republican State Central Committee (Box 57)
    - Request for contributions (Box 57)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - St. Joseph County Republican Committee (Box 57)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Van Buren County Republican Committee (Box 57)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Willkie, Wendell (Box 57)
  - 1945
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee (Box 57)
    - Bostetter, Martin J (Box 57)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Campaign support (Box 57)
    - Candidates for Congress (Box 57)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Endorsements (Box 57)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Hill, R.L. (Box 57)
    - Hoffman speeches (Box 57)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Pomeroy, Paul (Box 57)
    - Publicity (Box 57)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - Republican letters (Box 57)
    - Republican Congressional Committee (Box 57)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 57)
    - Republican Party (CEH newsletter and responses) (Box 57)
    - Republican State Central Committee (Box 57)
    - Republican organizations (Box 57)
    - Republican miscellaneous (Box 57)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
    - St. Joseph County Republican Committee (Box 57)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 57)
  - 1946
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Advertisements
      - Primary, 2 folders (Box 58)
      - General Election, 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 58)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Bacheller, Hazel (Box 58)
    - Barry County Republican Committee (Box 58)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee (Box 58)
    - Bostetter, Martin J (Box 58)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 58)
    - Campaign Contributions (Box 58)
    - Campaign materials (Box 58)
    - Campaign support (Box 58)
    - Congratulations (Box 58)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (political activities) (Box 58)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Election Statistics (Box 58)
    - Ellet, William C. (Box 58)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Fourth District Congressional Committee (Box 58)
    - Graf, John H. (Box 58)
    - Granger, F.L. (Box 58)
    - Hill, R.L. (Box 58)
    - Hoffman speeches, 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Hoffman (article about in Labor Digest) (Box 58)
    - Invitations (Box 58)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 58)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Newhouse, Walter P. (Box 58)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Petitions (Box 58)
    - Presidential candidates (Box 58)
    - Publicity (Box 58)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Republican Congressional Committee (Box 58)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 58)
    - Republican State Central Committee (Box 58)
    - Republican organizations (Box 58)
    - Republican publications (Box 58)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - St. Joseph County Republican Committee (Box 58)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Thomas, W.D. (Box 58)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
    - Van Buren County Republican Committee (Box 58)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 58)
  - 1947-1948
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Advertisements
      - Primary 1948 (Box 59)
      - General Election 1948 (Box 59)
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 59)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Bacheller, Hazel (Box 59)
    - Barry County Republican Committee (Box 59)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee (Box 59)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Campaign
      - Adverse (Box 59)
      - Commendatory material (Box 59)
      - Contributions (Box 59)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 59)
      - Offers of help (Box 59)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 59)
    - Complaints (Box 59)
    - Congratulations (Box 59)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (political activities) (Box 59)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Hill, R.L. (Box 59)
    - Hoffman speeches, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Hoffman remarks re "deal" with Southern Democrats (Box 59)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Newspapers
      - District (Box 59)
      - Out of District (Box 59)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Petitions, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Pomeroy, Paul (Box 59)
    - Presidential Candidates (Box 59)
    - Publicity (Box 59)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 59)
    - Republican Congressional Committee (Box 59)
    - Republican Leadership (Box 59)
    - Republican Legislative Program (Box 59)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 59)
    - Republican National Convention 1948 (Box 59)
    - Republican State Central Committee (Box 59)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - St. Joseph County Republican Committee (Box 60)
    - Speaking engagements (Box 60)
    - Van Buren County Republican Committee (Box 60)
    - Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Box 60)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Y (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
  - 1949-1950
    - Advertisements 1940, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 60)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Bacheller, Hazel (Box 60)
    - Barry County Republican Committee (Box 60)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee (Box 60)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Campaign
      - Commendatory (Box 60)
      - Contributions (Box 60)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 60)
      - Offers of support (Box 60)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 60)
    - Congratulations (Box 60)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight (Box 60)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Lamb, Ross H. (Box 60)
    - Lesinski, John (Box 60)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 60)
    - National Campaign (Box 60)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Petitions, 7 folders (Box 60)
    - Publicity, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
    - Republican Congressional Committee, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 61)
    - Republican State Central Committee (Box 61)
    - Republican organizations (Box 61)
    - Republican (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - St. Joseph County Republican Committee (Box 61)
    - Schoonard, Forest A. (Box 61)
    - Shafer, Chet (Box 61)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Van Buren County Republican Committee (Box 61)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Young Republicans (Box 61)
  - 1951-1952
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Adverse (Box 61)
    - Advertisements
      - Primary (Box 61)
      - General Election (Box 61)
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 61)
    - Allegan County Republican organizations (Box 61)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Bacheller, Hazel (Box 61)
    - Barry County Republican Committee (Box 61)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee (Box 61)
    - Bonine, G. Elwood (Box 61)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Campaign
      - Commendatory (Box 61)
      - Contributions (Box 61)
      - Lists (Box 61)
      - Offers of support, 4 folders (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 61)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 62)
    - Centerville Observer (Box 62)
    - Commendatory, 3 folders (Box 62)
    - Congratulations (Box 62)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - Delegates to state and national convention (Box 62)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight (Box 62)
    - Endorsements (Box 62)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - Fischer, Leslie H. (Box 62)
    - Fourth District Congressional Committee (Box 62)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - Hoffman speeches (Box 62)
    - Inauguration tickets (Box 62)
    - Invitations (Box 62)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - Kakebeeke, Lizzie (Box 62)
    - Kerr, William S. (Box 62)
    - Killian, Joseph E. (Box 62)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - Lamb, Rex (Box 62)
    - Lamb, Ross (Box 62)
    - Loupee, Sherman L. (Box 62)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - MacArthur, Douglas (Box 62)
    - Moody, Blair (Box 62)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - Nielsen, Axel (Box 62)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - Petitions (Box 62)
    - Potter, Charles E. (Box 62)
    - Presidential candidates (Box 62)
    - Press releases (Box 62)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 62)
    - Republican National Congressional Committee (Box 62)
    - Republican National Convention (tickets) (Box 62)
    - Republican Policy (Box 62)
    - Republican Program Coordinating Committee (Box 62)
    - Republican Publications (Box 62)
    - Republican State Central Committee, 2 folders (Box 62)
    - Republican organizations (Box 62)
    - Republican (miscellaneous) (Box 62)
    - Robinson, Glenn B. (Box 62)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - St. Joseph County Republican Committee (Box 63)
    - Southwestern Michigan Republican Association (Box 63)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 63)
    - State Politics (Box 63)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Taft, Robert A. (Box 63)
    - Universal Military Training Act letters (Box 63)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Van Buren County Republican Committee (Box 63)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Waste and extravagance (Box 63)
  - 1953-1954
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Adams, Dorothea (Box 63)
    - Advertisements
      - Primary (Box 63)